Guide to the New York Building Congress Records WAG.167
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Photographs, 1936-2008; 485661
  - Subseries VI:B: Events, 1944-2008; 485719
    - Hevesi, Alan: Event: Prints and Negatives, Oct 1998; 485893 (Box 38, Folder 29)
    - Holiday Party, 1996; 485892 (Box 38, Folder 30)
    - Holiday Show Entertainment: The Capital Steps (Grand Hyatt Hotel), Dec 20, 1988; 485891 (Box 38, Folder 31)
    - Howard J. Rubenstein Assoc., "Rebuilding New York": Contact Sheets, Oct 13, 1987; 485890 (Box 38, Folder 32)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (Grand Hyatt Hotel), Oct 29, 1996; 485889 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner Kick-Off: Prints and Negatives, Sep 1997; 485888 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (1), Oct 30, 1997; 485887 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (2), Oct 30, 1997; 485886 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (3), Oct 30, 1997; 485885 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (4), Oct 30, 1997; 485884 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (5), Oct 30, 1997; 485883 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (6), Oct 30, 1997; 485882 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (7), Oct 30, 1997; 485881 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (8), Oct 30, 1997; 485880 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (1), 1998; 485879 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (2), 1998; 485878 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (3), 1998; 485877 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (4), 1998; 485876 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (5), 1998; 485875 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (6), 1998; 485874 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (7), 1998; 485873 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner (8), 1998; 485872 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner: Kick-Off (Beacon Restaurant): Prints and Negatives, Sep 9, 1999; 485871 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Industry Recognition Dinner: Kick-Off Reception: Prints and Negatives, Sep 2000; 485870 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - John F. Kennedy International Airport Redevelopment: Slide, Dec 1997; 485869 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Luncheon, May 21, 1952; 485868 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Luncheon: NYBC and American Institute of Architects, Jun 26, 1952; 485867 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Luncheon: Annual, May 5, 1958; 485866 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Luncheon: Gillroy Testimonial, Nov 10, 1958; 485865 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Luncheon: New Members, Nov 17, 1958; 485864 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Luncheon: Annual (Hotel Commodore, Includes George Meany): Prints and Contact Sheets, Apr 27, 1967; 485863 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Luncheon: John V. Lindsay, Oct 10, 1972; 485862 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Luncheon: Unidentified, 1977; 485861 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Luncheon: Contact Sheets, May 11, 1978; 485860 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Luncheon: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 27, 1978; 485859 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Luncheon: Ed Koch, Sep 27, 1983; 485858 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Luncheon: Annual: Gerald Ford, Apr 4, 1984; 485857 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Luncheon: Ed Koch: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 6, 1986; 485856 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Luncheon: Senator Daniel P. Moynihan, Sep 14, 1987; 485855 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Luncheon: First Leadership Awards (Includes Edward Koch, Arthur Levitt, Jr., and Robert Wagner, Jr.): Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 29, 1988; 485854 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Luncheon: Richard Ravich: Prints and Contact Sheets, Oct 21, 1988; 485853 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Luncheon: Leadership Awards: Prints and Contact Sheets, Mar 28, 1989; 485852 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Luncheon: Leadership Awards: Prints and Negatives, 1996; 485851 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Luncheon: Millard, Oct 16, 1997; 485850 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Luncheon: Guy Molinari, 1997; 485849 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Luncheon: Gargano, Apr 23, 1998; 485848 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Luncheon: Gargano: Prints and Negatives, Apr 23, 1998; 485847 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Luncheon: Transportation: Prints and Negatives, Jun 1999; 485846 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Luncheon Committee Kick-Off, 1999; 485845 (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Luncheon: "T and I", 2000; 485844 (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Luncheon and Press Conference: Energy Report, Jan 25, 2001; 485843 (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Luncheon: Kick-Off Reception (Grand Havana Hotel), undated; 485842 (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Mayoral Meeting (?): Prints, Contact Sheet and Negatives, Nov 10, 1976(?); 485841 (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Membership Appreciation Event: Negatives, 1998; 485840 (Box 40, Folder 32)
    - NYBC Construction Forecast Seminar (McGraw Hill Building), Nov 1987; 485839 (Box 40, Folder 33)
    - NYBC - MIA [Marble Institute of America]: Five Year Plan, undated; 485838 (Box 40, Folder 34)
    - NYBC Update, Nov 6, 1992; 485837 (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - New Member Cocktail Party, Nov 17, 1958; 485836 (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - New York Association of Realty Managers Event: Prints and Negatives, undated; 485835 (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Officers Retirement Party, Sep 26, 1972; 485834 (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 26, 1945; 485833 (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 18, 1946; 485832 (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 26, 1947; 485831 (Box 40, Folder 41)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 1948; 485830 (Box 40, Folder 42)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 23, 1949; 485829 (Box 40, Folder 43)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 22, 1950; 485828 (Box 40, Folder 44)
    - Outing (North Hills Country Club), Jun 22, 1950; 485827 (Box 40, Folder 45)
    - Outing (N.H.S.C.) (1), Jun 21, 1951; 485826 (Box 40, Folder 46)
    - Outing (N.H.S.C.) (2), Jun 21, 1951; 485825 (Box 40, Folder 47)
    - Outing: Outing Committee, 1951; 485824 (Box 40, Folder 48)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (1), Jun 16, 1952; 485823 (Box 40, Folder 49)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (2), Jun 16, 1952; 485822 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club) (3), Jun 16, 1952; 485821 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Outing, 1953; 485820 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 14, 1954; 485819 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 13, 1955; 485818 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 11, 1956; 485817 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Outing, Jun 10, 1957; 485816 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 9, 1958; 485815 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Outing, Jun 15, 1959; 485814 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Outing: Outing Committee, Oct 1959; 485813 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Outing, Jun 1960; 485812 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 13, 1961; 485811 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1962; 485810 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1963; 485809 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Outing: Outing Committee, Sep 1963; 485808 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Outing, Jun 22, 1964; 485807 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Outing, Jun 28, 1965; 485806 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Outing, Jun 13, 1966; 485805 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 12, 1967; 485804 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 10, 1968; 485803 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 9, 1969; 485802 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 8, 1970; 485801 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), Jun 7, 1971; 485800 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Outing (Westchester Country Club), 1972; 485799 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 1973; 485798 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Outing, Jun 1974; 485797 (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - [Outing], circa 1976?; 485796 (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Outing, Jun 16, 1980; 485795 (Box 41, Folder 28)
    - [Outing], Jun 15, 1981; 485794 (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 28, 1982; 485793 (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Outing: Prints and Contact Sheets, Jun 18, 1983 or Jun 27, 1983; 485792 (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Outing: Contact Sheets, Jun 18, 1984; 485791 (Box 41, Folder 32)
    - Outing (1), 1985; 485790 (Box 41, Folder 33)
    - Outing (2), 1985; 485789 (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Outing: Contact Sheets, Jun 29, 1987; 485788 (Box 41, Folder 35)
    - Outing: Prints and Negatives, Jun 13, 1988; 485787 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Outing, 1994; 485786 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Outing, 1995; 485785 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Outing, 1996; 485784 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Outing, 1997; 485783 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Outing, 1998; 485782 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Outing, 1999; 485781 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Outing 1, undated; 485780 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Outing 2, undated; 485779 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Outing 3, undated; 485778 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Outing 4, undated; 485777 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Outings, 1969, undated; 485776 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Peter's Place Rededication Event: Prints and Negatives, May 24, 2000; 485775 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Presentation of Plaque to John Klenke: Prints and Negatives, May 25, 1960; 485774 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - P.W.C. Awards, Mar 16, 2000; 485773 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Reception: Peter J. Brennan, Dec 18, 1972; 485772 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Reception: George Fox Retirement, Sep 15, 1987; 485771 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - Reception: Holiday: Prints and Negatives, Dec 1996; 485770 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - Reception: State Legislature, 1996; 485769 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation: Prints and Negatives, Sep 30, 1997; 485768 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation, 1998; 485767 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation (1), Nov 4, 1999; 485766 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation (2), Nov 4, 1999; 485765 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Reception: C.B.B.D., Sep 24, 2000; 485764 (Box 42, Folder 24)
    - Reception: Membership Appreciation, Sep 2000; 485763 (Box 42, Folder 25)
    - Skidmore Birthday Party, Oct 16, 1950; 485762 (Box 42, Folder 26)
    - Skidmore Birthday Party (Hotel Baltimore), Apr 8, 1952; 485761 (Box 42, Folder 27)
    - Spitzer, Elliot: Event, circa 2008; 485760 (Box 42, Folder 28)
    - Staff [Event], circa 1999; 485759 (Box 42, Folder 29)
    - Surprise Party: Board of Governors Celebration of Past Presidents, Sep 29, 1955; 485758 (Box 42, Folder 30)
    - Times Square Event, [1998]; 485757 (Box 42, Folder 31)
    - Transportation Event with [Port Authority], Apr 1, 1996; 485756 (Box 42, Folder 32)
    - Tunnel Tour, Jan 9, 1973; 485755 (Box 42, Folder 33)
    - Unidentified [Awards] Event, undated; 485754 (Box 42, Folder 34)
    - Unidentified Event, Apr 8, 1963; 485753 (Box 42, Folder 35)
    - Unidentified Event, Jan 2000; 485752 (Box 42, Folder 36)
    - Unidentified Event: Prints and Negatives, Feb 27, 2001; 485751 (Box 42, Folder 37)
    - Unidentified Event 1 (1), undated; 485750 (Box 42, Folder 38)
    - Unidentified Event 1 (2), undated; 485749 (Box 42, Folder 39)
    - Unidentified Event 2 (1), undated; 485748 (Box 42, Folder 40)
    - Unidentified Event 2 (2), undated; 485747 (Box 42, Folder 41)
    - Unidentified Event 3, undated; 485746 (Box 42, Folder 42)
    - Unidentified Event 4, undated; 485745 (Box 42, Folder 43)
    - Unidentified Event 5, undated; 485744 (Box 42, Folder 44)
    - Unidentified Event 6 (Includes Claire Shulman), undated; 485743 (Box 42, Folder 45)
    - Unidentified Event 7: Negatives, undated; 485742 (Box 42, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified Event [Leadership Awards Luncheon?], undated; 485741 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified Event [Leadership Awards Luncheon?], undated; 485740 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified Event and Presentation 1: Prints and Contact Sheets, undated; 485739 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Unidentified Event and Presentation 2, undated; 485738 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified Event and Presentation 3, undated; 485737 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified [Formal Luncheon?] Event (1), circa 1960s - 1970s; 485736 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified [Formal Luncheon?] Event (2), circa 1960s - 1970s; 485735 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Unidentified Forum, 1997; 485734 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Unidentified Foundation Meeting: Prints and Negatives, Sep 27, 2000; 485733 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified Events, 1946-1963; 485732 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Unidentified Events, 1964 - 1979; 485731 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Unidentified Events: Negatives, 1995; 485730 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Unidentified Events, 1997; 485729 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified Events: Prints and Negatives, May 2000; 485728 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Unidentified Events (1), undated; 485727 (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Unidentified Events (2), undated; 485726 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified Events (3), undated; 485725 (Box 43, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified Events (4), undated; 485724 (Box 43, Folder 18)
    - Unidentified Events (5), undated; 485723 (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Unidentified Party, 1951; 485722 (Box 43, Folder 20)
    - Unidentified Speaker, undated; 485721 (Box 43, Folder 21)
    - Visit to Battery Park City Site, Mar 13, 1974; 485720 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Subseries VI:C: Portraits, 1931-1988; 485693
    - General, undated; 485718 (Box 43, Folder 23)
    - General: Negatives, undated; 485717 (Box 43, Folder 24)
    - Presidents (I), 1931-1969; 487273 (Box OS007, Folder 1)
    - Presidents (II), 1969-1987; 487274 (Box OS007, Folder 2)
    - A, 1971-1973, undated; 485716 (Box 43, Folder 25)
    - B (Includes Styles Bridges), 1953-1974; 485715 (Box 43, Folder 26)
    - C (Includes Edward Carlough and Robert Cutler): Prints and Negatives, 1945-1976; 485714 (Box 43, Folder 27)
    - D (Includes Robert W. Dowling), 1953-1988; 485713 (Box 43, Folder 28)
    - E, 1961-1975, undated; 485712 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    - F (Includes James Farley), 1953-1974, undated; 485711 (Box 43, Folder 30)
    - G, 1960-1974, undated; 485710 (Box 43, Folder 31)
    - H (Includes C. J. Haggerty, Charles Haines, Averell Harriman, Wallace K. Harrison and John F. Henning), 1936-1974, undated; 485709 (Box 43, Folder 32)
    - I, undated; 485708 (Box 43, Folder 33)
    - J, 1941-1967, undated; 485707 (Box 43, Folder 34)
    - K: Prints and Negatives, 1965-1977, undated; 485706 (Box 43, Folder 35)
    - L (Includes William L. Lauren, Arthur Levitt, Jr., and John V. Lindsay), 1962-1974; 485705 (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - M (Includes George Meany, Vice Admiral Ben Moreel, and Robert Moses), 1936-1975, undated; 485704 (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - N (Includes Richard Nixon and Lauris Norstad), 1964-1971, undated; 485703 (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - O (Includes William O'Dwyer), 1946-1975, undated; 485702 (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - P, 1965-1975, undated; 485701 (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - R (Includes Richard Ravitch and Nelson Rockefeller), 1947-1950, undated; 485700 (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - S (Includes Emil Schram, Louis Skidmore and Cardinal Francis Skidmore), 1941-1979; 485699 (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - T (Includes Bertram Tallamy, Thomas Thacher, Austin Tobin and John Tunney), 1936-1974; 485698 (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - U, 1974; 485697 (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - V, 1966, undated; 485696 (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - W (Includes Robert F. Wagner, Jr., Robert Weaver, Casper Weinberger, Grover Whalen and Malcolm Wilson), 1959-1977; 485695 (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - Z, 1948, 1985; 485694 (Box 43, Folder 47)
  - Subseries VI:D: Site Photographs, 1948-1974; 485688
    - Construction Sites: Slides and Negatives, undated; 485692 (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Demonstration of Honeywell Indoor Air Quality Diagnositics: Prints and Slides, undated; 485691 (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - Images of Albany, NY (Aerial), Jun 14, 1974; 485690 (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - NYBC Offices (Interior), 1948-1949; 485689 (Box 43, Folder 51)
  - Subseries VI:E: Other Formats and Oversize, 1943-1988; 485662
    - Rolled Photograph (Fun and Frolic) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], Dec 18, 1952; 485687 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Rolled Photograph (Fun and Frolic) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], 1953; 485686 (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Rolled Photograph (Fun and Frolic) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], 1954; 485685 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Rolled Photograph (Fun and Frolic) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], 1956; 485684 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Rolled Photograph (Gillroy Luncheon) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], undated; 485683 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Rolled Photographs (Joint Luncheon, NYBC and Producers' Council, Inc. (Hotel Baltimore); Fall Meeting of the Producers' Council, Inc.) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], Nov 11, 1943, Nov 29, 1944; Oct 2, 1947; 485682 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Rolled Photograph (Unidentified) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], undated; 485681 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Rolled Photographs (Unidentified) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], undated; 485680 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Rolled Photographs (Unidentified) [Restricted, consult Tamiment staff], undated; 485679 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Breakfast: Contact Sheets, undated; 485678 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - First Leadership Awards Luncheon (Grand Hyatt Hotel, Includes Ed Koch, Arthur Levitt, Jr. and RobertF. Wagner, Jr.), Mar 29, 1988; 485677 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Fun and Frolic, Dec 19, 1944; Dec 18, 1951; 485676 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Fun and Frolic: Contact Sheets, 1979; 1980; 485675 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - New York City Municipal Building, undated; 485674 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Portraits, undated; 485673 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Seminar (Grand Hyatt Hotel): Contact Sheets, undated; 485672 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Stereo Slides (1), 1952; 485671 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Stereo Slides (2), 1952; 485670 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Stereo Slides (3), 1952; 485669 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Stereo Slides (4), 1953; 485668 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Stereo Slides (5), 1953; 485667 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Stereo Slides (6), 1953; 485666 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Stereo Slides (7), 1953; 485665 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Stereo Slides (8), 1953; 485664 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Stereo Slides (9), 1953; 485663 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Series VII: Audio-Visual Materials, 1987-2004; 485644
  Series VII: Audio-Visual Materials, 1987-2004 contains VHS videotapes and audio cassettes of various events.
  - Subseries VII:A: Audiocassettes, 1987-1997; 485650
    - Rebuilding New York Conference Tape #1, Oct 13, 1987; 485660 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Rebuilding New York Conference Tape #2, Oct 13, 1987; 485659 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Rebuilding New York Conference Tape #3, Oct 13, 1987; 485658 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Rebuilding New York Conference Tape #4, Oct 13, 1987; 485657 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Rebuilding New York Conference Tape #5, Oct 13, 1987; 485656 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Rebuilding New York Conference Tape #6, Oct 13, 1987; 485655 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Rebuilding New York Conference Tape #7: Art Fox (closing), Oct 13, 1987; 485654 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Rebuilding New York Conference Tape: Lunch Speakers, Oct 13, 1987; 485653 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Louis Coletti on "Dialogue 101" (WCBS New York), 5am-5:30am, Jan 14, 1990; 485652 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Richard T. Anderson on WABC, 5:05pm`, Jun 10, 1997; 485651 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Subseries VII:B: Video (VHS), 2001-2004; 485645
    - Senator Hillary Rodham Clinton speaking at NYBC Luncheon Forum, Apr 30, 2001; 485649 (Box WAG ACCESS 1, Box 24, Folder 11)
    - NYBC World Trade Center Video (9/11 stills, footage, commentary; unidentified speakers), Nov 9, 2001; 485648 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - NYBC Dinner, Oct 23, 2003; 485647 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Leadership Awards Luncheon Video Presentation, May 20, 2004; 485646 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Series VIII: Unprocessed Materials, 1985-2017; 485634
  Series VIII: Unprocessed Materials, 1985-2017 contains materials related to the Industry Recognition Dinners and Leadership Awards Luncheons, public relations and membership, and the Council of Presidents, as well as photographs, publications, and VHS tapes from various events. This series also includes daily planners kept by NYBC President Richard T. Anderson from 1994-2016.
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist. The materials are arranged in the order in which they were received from the donor.
  - VHS Tapes of NYBC Events and Informational Programs, circa 1988-early 2000s; 485643 (Box 25)
  - VHS Tapes of NYBC Events and Informational Programs; Four Cassette Tapes of News Programs, Events, and Public Service Announcements; a CD titled "Urbanomics Presentation for the Manhattan Institute"; and Six DVDs of NYBC Dinners and "Women in Construction" Program, circa 1985-2011; 485642 (Box 26)
  - Industry Recognition Dinners and Leadership Awards Luncheons, 1990s; 485641 (Box 27)
  - Industry Recognition Dinners, Membership Survey, and Annual Reports, 1990s-2011; 485640 (Box 28)
  - Council of Presidents Meetings; Public Relations Materials; Membership Reports and Letters; NYC Olympic Bid Presentation; Industry Recognition Dinners; and Contact Sheets from Various Events, 1990-2001; 485639 (Box 29)
  - Photographs and Negatives from Various Events, 1998-2001, undated; 485638 (Box 30)
  - Photographs, 2002-2006, undated; 485637 (Box 31)
  - Photographs, Picture CD, and Audio CD, early 2000s; 485636 (Box 32)
  - Minutes, 1921-1989; 485635 (Box 33)
  - 2016 Accretion: NYBC Membership Directories, 2011-2014; 593412 (Box 47)
  - 2016 Accretion: ENR New York, 2011-2014; 593413 (Box 47)
  - 2016 Accretion: New York Construction, 2003-2007; 593414 (Box 47, Box 48)
  - 2016 Accretion: New York Construction News, 1997-2003; 593415 (Box 48, Box 49)
  - 2016 Accretion: After the Fall, 2002 May 26; 593416 (Box 50)
  - 2016 Accretion: Con Ed Footage, 2002-2005; 593417 (Box 50)
  - 2016 Accretion: Gargano Raw Footage, undated; 593418 (Box 50)
  - 2016 Accretion: Industry Recognition Dinner, Chuck Schumer, 2002 October 24; 593419 (Box 50)
  - 2016 Accretion: Industry Recognition Dinner, George Pataki, 2006 October 11; 593420 (Box 50)
  - 2016 Accretion: Jimmy Jones Interview, 2003; 593421 (Box 50)
  - 2016 Accretion: Marilyn Jordan Taylor Off Camera Voice Over, 2003; 593422 (Box 50)
  - 2016 Accretion: Hillary Clinton Dinners and Luncheons, 2002-2004; 593423 (Box 51)
  - 2016 Accretion: Luncheon on Transit News Magazine, 2004; 593424 (Box 51)
  - 2016 Accretion: OEM on PILE, 2001; 593425 (Box 51)
  - 2016 Accretion: Peckar, Rudin, and Malloy Tribute, 2002 October 24; 593426 (Box 51)
  - 2016 Accretion: Skanska, 2000; 593427 (Box 51)
  - 2016 Accretion: World Trade Center Tributes, 2002-2004; 593428 (Box 52, Box 53)
  - 2016 Accretion: NYBC Luncheon and Dinner Video Recordings, 2001-2008; 593429 (Box 54, Box 55)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Administrative Documents, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593441 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Board Meetings, 2011-2015 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Committee and Task Force Meetings, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593431 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Events, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593432 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Executive Committee, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593433 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Management Commitee, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593434 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Media, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593435 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)
  - 2016 Accretion: Electronic Records: Membership, 2011-2015; TW_WAG_167_1; 593442 (Disk TW_WAG_167_1)